MARC ROUSAVY

Software Developer



mrousavy.github.io



mrousavy@outlook.com



/in/mrousavy



mrousavy

Skills

Overview



Programming

C# • Java • JavaEE

Go • Python • SQL

C • C++ • Swift

JavaScript • TypeScript • Node

Projects -

ImgurSniper - An easy to use screenshot tool for Windows in C# .NET WPF BrabeNetz - A multithreaded high performance supervised neural network trained for digit recognition in C++ Jellyfish - A fast, clean and lightweight MVVM library for writing maintainable

Forecast - A specialized project, employee and infrastructure management tool.

Education

2014 - 2019 HTL (Informational Technology)

2010 - 2014 **Secondary School** (Informational Technology) HS, St. Andrä Wördern

Experience

Feb 2018 - **Software Developer** Present

AGRANA Beteiligungs-AG

TGM, Vienna

 Currently involved in developing C# .NET Windows applications, mobile apps, Azure services, high availability services and SAP applications

Sep 2018 -Apr 2019 **Software Developer**

Hutchison Drei Austria GmbH

 In a team of four as a diploma project, we created the "Drei Friendfinder" Android and iOS Application paired with the Firebase and Firestore Node.js backend

Feb 2018 -May 2018 Software Developer

Hutchison Drei Austria GmbH

 In a team of four, created the Prototype "Drei Friendfinder" Android Application paired with the Firebase microservice Node.js backend

Jan 2018 -May 2018 Software Engineer

Hexagon PPM

 Built a major C# .NET application using MVVM WPF GUI and EntityFramework for managing projects and employees.

Aug 2017 -Sep 2017

17 - Software Engineer

Hexagon PPM

 Built a major VB .NET application using MVVM WPF GUI for sorting projects and attributes on databases

Jul 2017 -Aug 2017 **Software Developer**

AGRANA Beteiligungs-AG

Involved in developing C# .NET applications & high availability services, as well as creating a mobile app and extending an ASP.MVC website

Jul 2016 -

Software Developer

AGRANA Beteiligungs-AG

Aug 2016

Involved in extending small existing C# .NET applications & services

vice

Aug 2015 - Software Engineer

Gemeindeamt Muckendorf

Sep 2015

Created an android application for the local community

Jul 2015 -

Public Service

Gemeindeamt Muckendorf

Aug 2015

Sorted files and plots of land

Licenses

2017 Linux Essentials

Cisco NetAcad Linux Essentials

· Website